Thank you for calling CloudServe support, this is Jules Becker. How can I help you today?
Hi, my name is Jordan. I have an account with you and I need help with billing question.
I can help with that. Can I get the email address on the account?
It's jordan_ramirez@gmail.example.
Got it. Pulling up your account now.
I have your account here, Tundra Foods Systems, on the business plan.
Can we resolve this on the phone?
Of course. We'll handle this end-to-end on the call.
For billing question, the steps on my side are…
Ok, sounds good.
[10-15 seconds working in the system]
Ok, I've filed the request and routed it for the right approvals.
Great. Anything else I need to do?
Nope, all set on our side. Thanks for calling.
Anything else I can help with today?
All set, thanks.
Thanks for calling CloudServe. Have a good day.